Office of the Vice-President, Finance and Administration fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Office of the Vice-President, Finance and Administration fonds
1966 - 1984
F-28
5.38 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Office of the Vice-President, Finance and Administration
The Office of Vice-President, Finance and Administration was originally established by the Board of Governors on 21 June 1968, under the title Vice-President, Administration. The general administration of the University was originally a function of the President, who by 1966 had delegated this responsibility to a senior administrator. This administrator oversaw a number of administrative units, including the Bursar, Registrar, General Services, Facility Planning, and the Library. In 1968, the Office of Vice-President, Administration was created, and was responsible for finance, physical plant and planning, purchasing, personnel, ancillary services, and athletics and recreation. Each of these units was headed by a director.
By 1981, responsibility for finance, including the office of Bursar, was moved to a newly created Executive Director of Finance, which by 1985 was renamed Vice-President, Finance and in 1988, Vice-President, Financial Services. Both the Vice-Presidents Administration and Financial Services reported directly to the President. In 1993, the two separate offices were rejoined to form the Office of Vice-President, Finance and Administration.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the body.
The fonds of the Vice-President, Finance and Administration consists of records made and received in the course of carrying out the general administration of the University. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; general supervision of units reporting to the Vice-President; participation in university committees; liaison with internal and external bodies such as the various faculties, employee associations and unions, other universities, associations, and municipalities; budget preparation; correspondence with various individuals and bodies; and speeches and engagements undertaken as a representative of the University. The types of documents include meeting agenda and minutes, correspondence, memoranda, reports, publications, and brochures.
Since their inception, the Offices of the Vice-President Finance and Administration and its predecessors have organized their records according to a file classification system. Following transfer to the Archives, however, the original order of the records was compromised by the re-arrangement carried out by the archivist. In the process of the initial archival arrangement, records were re-arranged into artificial record groups and series, borrowing titles from the original classification system.
This re-arrangement scheme created three separate record groups for the Offices of Vice-President Administration, Vice-President Finance, and Bursar. Within the Vice-President Administration record group, files were arranged into three broad categories: statutory authorities and the higher bodies such as the President and the Board of Governors to which the Vice-President reported; administrative departments reporting to the Vice-President, Administration; and external relations with persons and bodies both within the University and external to it. Committee records were removed and placed in an artificial subgroup titled "Vice-President's Committees." These records have now been re-integrated into the description in the series titled "Committees."
No attempt has been made to physically re-arrange records into their original order. The records of the once separate groups of Vice-President, Administration; Vice-President, Finance; and Bursar are now re-integrated into this description of the proper successor body. The titles given to series are derived from the original file index, except in the case of the series "Memoranda," which was originally titled "University."
Further accruals to the Archives will be arranged in conformity with the file classification system in place in the Vice-President Administration and Finance Office. New series numbers will be assigned on the basis of that classification system. Consult the archivist for further information.
Suart, George; Scott, Ernest M.
The records were transferred directly from the Office of the Vice-President, Administration.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed (as of September 2002: 3.67 m., 1970-1985). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventories to the fonds of the Office of the President (F-27), Board of Governors (F-33), and Facilities Management (F-11).
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- Statutory authorities, 1967 - 1981; F-28-1; 6 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to the relationship of the Vice-President with the President, Board of Governors, and government. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Organization, 1968 - 1974; F-28-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - Organization, 1976 - 1978; F-28-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Organization: reorganization, 1967; F-28-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Policies and Procedures, 1975 - 1979; F-28-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Board of Governors, 1978; F-28-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - University President, 1970 - 1981; F-28-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Government, 1976 - 1979; F-28-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
- Correspondence, 1968 - 1984; F-28-2; 83 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the chronologically arranged correspondence of the Vice-President, Administration.
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1968; F-28-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-28-2-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-28-2-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 28-2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-28-2-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1972; F-28-2-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1972; F-28-2-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1972; F-28-2-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1972; F-28-2-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 28-3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-28-2-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 28-4)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-28-2-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 28-5)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-28-2-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 28-6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-28-2-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1981; F-28-2-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
  - Correspondence, 1968 - 1984; F-28-2-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 28-7)
- Administrative departments, 1966 - 1984; F-28-3; 1.54 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the relationship between the Vice-President, Administration and the various departments and units which reported to that office. These included the Bursar, Ancillary Services, Computing, Personnel, Athletics and Recreation, and Physical Plant and Planning. The series includes correspondence, memoranda and reports.
  - General, 1970 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Activity Reports (Administrative Assistant), 1974 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Activity Reports (Administrative Assistant), 1976; F-28-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Crisis, 1968 - 1970; F-28-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Departmental Activities, 1969 - 1971; F-28-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Departmental Activities, 1972; F-28-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Departmental Activities, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Departmental Activities, 1974; F-28-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Meetings, 1976 - 1977; F-28-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Committee: Administrative Assistants' Meetings, 1977 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Finance, 1969 - 1970; F-28-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-8)
  - Finance, 1973 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Finance, 1981; F-28-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Finance-Budget, 1969 - 1970; F-28-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Finance-Budget, 1971; F-28-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Finance-Budget, 1972 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Finance-Budget, 1976 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Finance-Capital Funds, 1976 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Finance-Cost Studies, 1970 - 1972; F-28-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Ancillary Services, 1971 - 1980; F-28-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Ancillary Services - Food Services, 1968 - 1970; F-28-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Ancillary Services - Food Services, 1971 - 1974; F-28-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 28-9)
  - Ancillary Services - Food Services, 1975 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 28-10)
  - Ancillary Services - Food Services, 1977 - 1981; F-28-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 28-10)
  - Ancillary Services - Duplicating and Printing, 1973 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 28-10)
  - Ancillary Services - Central Stores, 1970 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 28-10)
  - Ancillary Services - Parking, Traffic and Security, 1968 - 1971; F-28-3-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 28-10)
    Restricted in whole
  - Ancillary Services - Parking, Traffic and Security, 1972 - 1973; F-28-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 28-10)
  - Ancillary Services - Parking, Traffic and Security, 1974 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 28-10)
  - Ancillary Services - Parking, Traffic and Security, 1977 - 1981; F-28-3-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 28-11)
    File contains correspondence of the Vice-President, Administration with or related to Ancillary Services. Topics include theft on campus, vandalism, security incidents and issues, parking policy and space planning, parking violations, and responsibilities relating to radiological safety. Record types include correspondence and some reports.
  - Athletics and Recreation, 1970 - 1972; F-28-3-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 28-11)
  - Athletics and Recreation, 1973 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 28-11)
  - Athletics and Recreation, 1976 - 1981; F-28-3-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 28-11)
  - Bursar, 1970 - 1972; F-28-3-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 28-11)
  - Bursar, 1973 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 28-11)
  - Bursar, 1976 - 1978; F-28-3-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 28-11)
  - Computing, 1966 - 1970; F-28-3-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 28-11)
  - Computing, 1971 - 1973; F-28-3-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 28-12)
  - Computing, 1974 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 28-12)
  - Computing, 1976 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 28-12)
  - Personnel, 1970 - 1971; F-28-3-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 28-12)
  - Personnel, 1972 - 1973; F-28-3-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 28-12)
  - Personnel, 1974 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 28-12)
  - Personnel, 1976 - 1977; F-28-3-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing, 1966; F-28-3-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing, 1972; F-28-3-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Benefits, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Benefits, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Modified Work Week, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Pensions, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Pensions, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Salaries, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Benefits, 1974; F-28-3-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Modified Work Week, 1975; F-28-3-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Pensions, 1976; F-28-3-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 28-13)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Pensions and Study Leave, 1977; F-28-3-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 28-14)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Hay System, 1978; F-28-3-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 28-14)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Hay System, 1979; F-28-3-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 28-14)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Salaries, 1979; F-28-3-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 28-14)
  - Personnel - Staffing - Hay System, 1980; F-28-3-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 28-14)
  - Personnel - Staffing - APSA, 1981; F-28-3-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 28-14)
  - Personnel - Charts and Tables: Re Hay System, 1981; F-28-3-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 28-14)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Unions, 1967 - 1973; F-28-3-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 28-14)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Unions, 1974; F-28-3-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 28-15)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Unions, 1975; F-28-3-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 28-15)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Unions, 1975; F-28-3-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 28-15)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Unions, 1975; F-28-3-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 28-15)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Unions, 1976; F-28-3-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 28-15)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Unions, 1976; F-28-3-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 28-15)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Unions, 1976; F-28-3-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 28-15)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Strikes, 1978 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
    Open
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Strikes, 1976; F-28-3-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Strikes, 1977; F-28-3-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Strikes, 1977; F-28-3-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Strikes, 1978; F-28-3-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Strikes, 1979; F-28-3-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee Relations - Strikes, 1979; F-28-3-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Personnel - Labour/Employee: Labour Management Committee, 1978 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Labour/Employee Relations: Labour Management Committee, 1975 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Labour/Employee Relations: Labour Management Committee, 1981 - 1983; F-28-3-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 28-16)
  - Personnel - Vice-President, Administration, 1974 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Vice-President, Academic, 1974; F-28-3-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Bursar, 1971 - 1972; F-28-3-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Computing, 1974 - 1981; F-28-3-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 28-17)